Guide to the Seal and Serpent Society of Cornell University records, 1906-2009.
Seal and Serpent Society of Cornell University records, 1906-2009.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Seal and Serpent Society of Cornell University records, 1906-2009.
37-4-871
Seal and Serpent Society of Cornell University.
12.5 cubic ft.
Printed material, constitution, bylaws, meeting minutes, financial records, construction plans and specifications, photographs and correspondence.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Materials relating to the Seal and Serpent, a local fraternity founded at Cornell in 1905.
ORGANIZATIONAL HISTORY
Local fraternity founded at Cornell in 1905.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Records include constitutions and bylaws, certificate of incorporation, 1919; correspondence, 1916-1965; Board of Directors', annual, and committee meeting minutes, 1906-1986; financial records, and construction plans and specifications; photographs, 1942-1991; many letters, accounts, plans, and other items relating to the presidency, beginning in 1923, of Creed Walsh Fulton ('09), during which a new house for the Society was planned, financed, and opened in 1927. Also, directories (incomplete run); directory questionnaires and personal data sheets; The Snake, the publication of the group; a printed petition, ca. 1907, to the executive board and chapters of Phi Kappa Sigma fraternity from the members of Seal and Serpent, asking for authority to establish a chapter of that fraternity at Cornell and including information concerning the fraternity system at Cornell at that time, a brief history of Seal and Serpent, a building fund prospectus, a group photograph, and a list of the petitioners with accompanying personal data; rush booklets; and miscellaneous items relating to the fraternity.
Also, group photograph including Alvin W. King (Class of 1907), one of the founding members of Seal and Serpent and bearer of pin number 1. CD with photographs of a ROTC event in September 2009.
Original bellows purchased as part of the original furnishings for the Lodge and selected by O. (Ornan) Hibbard Waltz, in 1927.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Seal and Serpent Society of Cornell University.; Walsh, Creed Fulton.; Cornell University--Students.; Cornell University--Societies, etc.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
Access Restrictions:
Access restricted to written permission from the Society President, Vice President or Historian.
CONTAINER LIST
- Minutes and bylaws - annual meetings; Board of Directors; committee meetings and reports, May 18, 1907-October 1, 1919 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Minutes and bylaws, June 20, 1919-November 22, 1920 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Minutes and bylaws, October 14, 1921-November 1, 1924 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Minutes and bylaws, May 24, 1924-May 21, 1927 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Minutes and bylaws, February 16, 1928-May 24, 1930 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Minutes and bylaws, May 24, 1931-October 13, 1934 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Minutes and bylaws, May 11, 1933-November 18, 1937 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Minutes and bylaws, March 15, 1933-December 4, 1940 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Minutes and bylaws, May 7, 1941-June 3, 1947 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Minutes and bylaws, May 15, 1949-December 5, 1952 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Minutes and bylaws, 1953 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Minutes and bylaws, 1954 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Minutes and bylaws, February 15-September 22, 1955 (Box 2, Folder 13)
- Minutes and bylaws, 1956 (Box 2, Folder 14)
- Minutes and bylaws, 1957 (Box 2, Folder 15)
- Minutes and bylaws, 1958 (Box 2, Folder 16)
- Minutes and bylaws, 1959 (Box 2, Folder 17)
- Minutes and bylaws, 1960 (Box 2, Folder 18)
- Minutes and bylaws, May 21, 1961-October 19, 1963 (Box 2, Folder 19)
- Also undated bylaws and miscellaneous correspondence, 1916-1924 (Box 2, Folder 19)
- Correspondence, January 1925-December 1926 (Box 3)
- Correspondence, January 1927-December 1939 (Box 4)
- Correspondence, 1940-1950 (Box 5)
- Correspondence, 1951-1962 (Box 6)
- Correspondence, 1963-1965 (Box 7)
- Circular letters, 1925-1927 (Box 7)
- Correspondence, undated (Box 7)
- Correspondence, 1970's-1980's and miscellany (Box 8)
- The Snake backissues (More Snakes in Box 11), 1914-1992 (Box 9)
- Printed membership directories, 1913, 1915, 1925, 1928, 1937 (2), 1948 (2), 1952, 1955, 1960 (Box 10, Folder 1)
- Directory information, A-M, 1941 (Box 10, Folder 2)
- Directory information, N-Z, 1941 (Box 10, Folder 3)
- Directory - personal data sheets, A-H, 1946 (Box 10, Folder 4)
- Directory - personal data sheets, J-R, 1946 (Box 10, Folder 5)
- Directory - personal data sheets, S-Z, 1946 (Box 10, Folder 6)
- Directory, A-C, 1952 (Box 10, Folder 7)
- Directory, D-G, 1952 (Box 10, Folder 8)
- Directory, H-M, 1952 (Box 10, Folder 9)
- Directory, N-S, 1952 (Box 10, Folder 10)
- Directory, T-Z, 1952 (Box 10, Folder 11)
- Directory (second notices), 1952 (Box 10, Folder 12)
- Directory - final lists for directory, 1952 (Box 10, Folder 13)
- Directory - membership lists and miscellaneous information, 1952 (Box 10, Folder 14)
- Petition from Seal and Serpent to Phi Kappa Sigma fraternity, asking for authority to establish a chapter of PKS at Cornell, and relevant information, ca. 1907 (Box 10)
- Other miscellaneous material (Box 10)
- Snake and some other publications and newsletters, February 1965 (Box 11)
- Snake and some other publications and newsletters, April 1962 (Box 11)
- Snake and some other publications and newsletters, February 1960 (Box 11)
- Snake and some other publications and newsletters, June 1960 (Box 11)
- Snake and some other publications and newsletters, September 1959 (Box 11)
- Snake and some other publications and newsletters, February 1959 (Box 11)
- Snake and some other publications and newsletters, May 1958 (Box 11)
- Snake and some other publications and newsletters, August 1954 (Box 11)
- Snake and some other publications and newsletters, April 1953 (Box 11)
- Snake and some other publications and newsletters, December 1951 (Box 11)
- Snake and some other publications and newsletters, August 1950 (Box 11)
- Snake and some other publications and newsletters, April 1950 (Box 11)
- Snake and some other publications and newsletters, December 1949 (Box 11)
- Snake and some other publications and newsletters, December 1948 (Box 11)
- Snake and some other publications and newsletters, August 1948 (Box 11)
- Snake and some other publications and newsletters, March 1948 (Box 11)
- Snake and some other publications and newsletters, August 1947 (Box 11)
- Snake and some other publications and newsletters, January 1943 (Box 11)
- Snake and some other publications and newsletters, August 1942 (Box 11)
- Snake and some other publications and newsletters, November 1941 (Box 11)
- Snake and some other publications and newsletters, June 1941 (Box 11)
- Snake and some other publications and newsletters, January 1941 (Box 11)
- Snake and some other publications and newsletters, October 1938 (Box 11)
- Snake and some other publications and newsletters, April 1938 (Box 11)
- Snake and some other publications and newsletters, September 1937 (Box 11)
- Snake and some other publications and newsletters, March 1937 (Box 11)
- Snake and some other publications and newsletters, November 1936 (Box 11)
- Snake and some other publications and newsletters, April 1934 (Box 11)
- Snake and some other publications and newsletters, July 1933 (Box 11)
- Snake and some other publications and newsletters, August 1932 (Box 11)
- Snake and some other publications and newsletters, October 1930 (Box 11)
- Snake and some other publications and newsletters, December 1929 (Box 11)
- Snake and some other publications and newsletters, August 1929 (Box 11)
- Super secret (Box 12)
- Recent minutes (Box 12)
- House Lodge stuff (Box 12)
- Photographs (Box 13)
- Social stuff (Box 13)
- House sketch (Box 13)
- Guestbook 1967-1983 (Box 13)
- ROTC event (CD-634) 2009 (Box 13)
- Other materials (Box 13)
- Financial records from old Boxes 8, 9, and 13, and new (Box 14)
- Party souvenirs, 1935-1942 (Box 15)
- hat (Box 15)
- CU Seal + Serpent mug 1948 (Box 15)
- 3 tee shirts (Box 15)
- Sweat shirt (Box 15)
- Framed certificate "Leslie Arthur Dittman, Uncle (Box 15)
- Greenberg (05) on Conan (sp?), CD-635 (Box 15)
- Photographs (Box 16)
- Composites (Box 16)
- Guestbook 1960-1971 (Box 16)
- Misc. Finances, 2000+ (Box 17, Folder 1)
- Misc. Finances, 2000+ (Box 17, Folder 2)
- Misc. Finances, 2000+ (Box 17, Folder 3)
- Misc. Finances, 2000+ (Box 17, Folder 4)
- Misc. Finances, 2000+ (Box 17, Folder 5)
- Misc. Finances, 2000+ (Box 17, Folder 6)
- Misc. Finances, 2000+ (Box 17, Folder 7)
- Misc. Finances, 2000+ (Box 17, Folder 8)
- Misc. Finances, 2000+ (Box 17, Folder 9)
- Misc. Finances, 2000+ (Box 17, Folder 10)
- Misc. Finances, 2000+ (Box 17, Folder 11)
- Bills, 2000+ (Box 17, Folder 12)
- Bills, 2000+ (Box 17, Folder 13)
- Taxes, 1999-2001 (Box 17, Folder 14)
- Housing and Parking Contracts, 2002 (Box 17, Folder 15)
- Housing Contracts, 2000 (Box 17, Folder 16)
- Housing Contracts, 2001 (Box 17, Folder 17)
- Housing Contracts, 2003 (Box 17, Folder 18)
- Housing Packet, 2000 (Box 17, Folder 19)
- Housing "Stuff", 2000-2001 (Box 17, Folder 20)
- House Manager Items, 2001-2002 (Box 17, Folder 21)
- Misc. Information, 2002-2003 (Box 17, Folder 22)
- Misc. Finances, 2001-2003 (Box 17, Folder 23)
- House Manager Folder, 2002-2003 (Box 17, Folder 24)
- Various Manuals (Box 17, Folder 25)
- Misc. Finances, 1970s and 1980s (Box 17, Folder 26)
- House Renovation Records, 1970s (Box 18, Folder 1)
- Construction Account, 1984-1986 (Box 18, Folder 2)
- "Background of Mortgage", 1982-1985 (Box 18, Folder 3)
- Construction Account, 1987-1989 (Box 18, Folder 4)
- Condition Assessment Report, 1998 (Box 18, Folder 5)
- Floor-plans and Renovation, 1983 (Box 18, Folder 6)
- Blueprints (Box 18, Folder 7)
- City of Ithaca Inspections and Permits (Box 18, Folder 8)
- Contracts and House Manager Guide, 1998-2001 (Box 18, Folder 9)
- Misc. Alumni Fund Finances, 1970s (Box 18, Folder 10)
- Misc. Alumni Fund Finances, 1970s (Box 18, Folder 11)
- Alumni Financial Report, 1976-1977 (Box 18, Folder 12)
- Alumni Folder, 1977-1979 (Box 18, Folder 13)
- Sun First National Bank As Trustee, 1976 (Box 18, Folder 14)
- Misc Alumni Fund Finances, 1980s (Box 18, Folder 15)
- Alumni Financial Reports, 1985-1988 (Box 18, Folder 16)
- Alumni Financial Reports, 1988-1989 (Box 18, Folder 17)
- Norstar Bank, Alumni Fund, 1985-1989 (Box 18, Folder 18)
- Statements- Monthly Rent Reserve, 1980-1990 (Box 18, Folder 19)
- "Friend Raising", 1987 (Box 18, Folder 20)
- The Snake and Homecoming, Early 1970s (Box 18, Folder 21)
- 75th Anniversary Planning, 1980 (Box 18, Folder 22)
- Student Management Corporation Statements, 1991-1994 (Box 18, Folder 23)
- SMC Statements, 1987-1991 (Box 18, Folder 24)
- Tax Returns, 1989 (Box 18, Folder 25)
- Taxes, 1980s (Box 18, Folder 26)
- Taxes, 1980s (Box 18, Folder 27)
- Summer Housing Contracts, 1999 (Box 18, Folder 28)
- Treasurer's Binder Contents (Box 18, Folder 29)
- Misc Finances, 1970s-1980s (Box 18, Folder 30)
- Treasurer Folder, 1996-1999 (Box 19, Folder 1)
- Budgets, 1996-1999 (Box 19, Folder 2)
- Paid Invoice Journals, 1996-1999 (Box 19, Folder 3)
- Balance Sheets and Income Statements, 1996-1999 (Box 19, Folder 4)
- Mortgage and Bank, 1996-1999 (Box 19, Folder 5)
- Aged Accounts Payable, 1996-1999 (Box 19, Folder 6)
- House Detail, 1996-1999 (Box 19, Folder 7)
- Misc Finances, 1996-1999 (Box 19, Folder 8)
- Accounts Receivable, 1996-1999 (Box 19, Folder 9)
- Bills, 1996-1999 (Box 19, Folder 10)
- Insurance, 1996-1999 (Box 19, Folder 11)
- Taxes, 1996-1999 (Box 19, Folder 12)
- Other Contracts, 1996-1999 (Box 19, Folder 13)
- Blank Forms and Contracts, 1996-1999 (Box 19, Folder 14)
- Bank Deposits, 1996-1999 (Box 19, Folder 15)
- Room Contracts, 1996-1999 (Box 19, Folder 16)
- SMC, 1996-1999 (Box 19, Folder 17)
- Bursar Billing, 1996-1999 (Box 19, Folder 18)
- Social Stuff, 1940-1991 (Box 19, Folder 19)
- Spring Formal, 1991 (Box 19, Folder 20)
- Misc Items, Spring 1991 (Box 19, Folder 21)
- IFC Stuff, 1991 (Box 19, Folder 22)
- Meeting Notes, 1991 (Box 19, Folder 23)
- Rules (Box 19, Folder 24)
- Christmas Carols (Box 19, Folder 25)
- Events, 1995-1997 (Box 19, Folder 26)
- Calenders, 1996 (Box 19, Folder 27)
- Services, 1996 (Box 19, Folder 28)
- Registration, 1996 (Box 19, Folder 29)
- Social Chair Guidelines, 1997 (Box 19, Folder 30)
- Budgets, 1987-1990 (Box 19, Folder 31)
- Misc Finances, 1996-1997 (Box 19, Folder 32)
- Board of Director Meetings (Box 20, Folder 1)
- Meeting Minutes and Agendas, 1980s (Box 20, Folder 2)
- Synopsis (Box 20, Folder 3)
- Board of Directors, Member, and Alumni Lists, 1985-1991 (Box 20, Folder 4)
- Summer Conference, 1992 (Box 20, Folder 5)
- Homecoming, 2000-2001 (Box 20, Folder 6)
- Homecoming and The Snake, 1989-1990 (Box 20, Folder 7)
- Homecoming and Reunion, 1990-1997 (Box 20, Folder 8)
- Homecoming Finances (Box 20, Folder 9)
- Fraternity Newsletters, 1976-1990 (Box 20, Folder 10)
- Memorabilia- Catalogs (Box 20, Folder 11)
- Memorabilia- Correspondences and Rules, 1990-2010 (Box 20, Folder 12)
- Memorabilia- Orders, 1990-2002 (Box 20, Folder 13)
- Alumni Board of Directors, 1996 (Box 20, Folder 14)
- The Snake, 1938 (Box 20, Folder 15)
- The Snake and Alumni News, 1979-1996 (Box 20, Folder 16)
- End of Year Report, 2005-2006 (Box 20, Folder 17)
- General Information- Bylaws, 1998 (Box 20, Folder 18)
- Miscellaneous Proposals and Board Meeting Plans (Box 20, Folder 19)
- Pledging, 1990s (Box 20, Folder 20)
- Pledging, 1990s (Box 20, Folder 21)
- Proposals and Correspondences, 1980s (Box 20, Folder 22)
- "Promises of Brotherhood" Poems, 1998 (Box 20, Folder 23)
- Creative Works (Drawings, Poems, Etc) (Box 20, Folder 24)
- Stationary (Box 20, Folder 25)
- Renovation Finances, 1980s (Box 20, Folder 26)
- Finances, 1990s (Box 20, Folder 27)
- IFC- Judicial Incidents, 2000-2001 (Box 20, Folder 28)
- Advertisements and Catalog Pages (Box 20, Folder 29)
- Events, Ads, and Articles, 2010 (Box 20, Folder 30)
- Household Renovations, 2002 (Box 20, Folder 31)
- IFC Annual Self-Evaluation Report, 1990-1991, 1994-1995 (Box 20, Folder 32)
- "A Brief History" (Box 20, Folder 33)
- Safety Inspections, 1990 (Box 20, Folder 34)
- Misc Agendas and Goals, 1990 (Box 20, Folder 35)
- Chapter Report "Originals", 1991-1992 (Box 20, Folder 36)
- "Pledge Education" (Box 20, Folder 37)
- "Hellmaster" - Initiation Information (Box 20, Folder 38)
- Chapter Report, 1999-2000 (Box 20, Folder 39)
- Chapter Report, 1996-1997 (Box 20, Folder 40)
- Greek Life Annual Chapter Self-Evaluation Report, Final, 1990 (Box 20, Folder 41)
- Self-Evaluation Report, Final, 1991 (Box 20, Folder 42)
- Rush, 2002-2003 (Box 20, Folder 43)
- Pledge Education Guide (Box 20, Folder 44)
- Pledge Education, 2004 (Box 20, Folder 45)
- Resumes and Cover Letters, 1980s (Box 20, Folder 46)
- Miscellaneous Correspondences and Items (Box 20, Folder 47)
- Miscellaneous Receipts, 1980s (Box 21, Folder 1)
- Financial Correspondences (Box 21, Folder 2)
- Budget, 1978-1979 (Box 21, Folder 3)
- Budget, 1979-1980 (Box 21, Folder 4)
- Budget, 1980-1981 (Box 21, Folder 5)
- Budget, 1981-1982 (Box 21, Folder 6)
- Budget, 1982-1983 (Box 21, Folder 7)
- Budget, 1983-1984 (Box 21, Folder 8)
- Budget, 1984-1985 (Box 21, Folder 9)
- Budget, 1985-1986 (Box 21, Folder 10)
- Budget, 1986-1987 (Box 21, Folder 11)
- Budget, 1987-1988 (Box 21, Folder 12)
- Payments, 1979-1980 (Box 21, Folder 13)
- Misc Finances, 1970s (Box 21, Folder 14)
- Payments, 1980-1981 (Box 21, Folder 15)
- Bond (Box 21, Folder 16)
- Profit and Loss Statements, 1979-1988 (Box 21, Folder 17)
- Statements of Activities and Receipts, 1980s (Box 21, Folder 18)
- Miscellanoeus Finances, 1980s (Box 21, Folder 19)
- Miscellaneous Finances, 1983-1991 (Box 21, Folder 20)
- Payroll Cash Vouchers, 1986 (Box 21, Folder 21)
- Billing Sheets and Journal Entries, 1989 (Box 21, Folder 22)
- Balance Sheets, 1989-1993 (Box 21, Folder 23)
- Miscellanous Finances, 1992-1993 (Box 21, Folder 24)
- Financials- Merrill Lynch, 1981-1985 (Box 21, Folder 25)
- Financials- Merrill Lynch, 1985-1989 (Box 21, Folder 26)
- First National Ithaca- Miscellaneous Statements of Accounts, 1970s (Box 21, Folder 27)
- First National Ithaca- Miscellaneous Statements of Accounts, 1970s (Box 21, Folder 28)
- Tompkins County Trust Company, 1985-1989 (Box 21, Folder 29)
- SMC, 2000-2002 (Box 22, Folder 1)
- Bursar Billing, 2002 (Box 22, Folder 2)
- Room Contracts, 1999 (Box 22, Folder 3)
- Bank Deposits, 2000-2002 (Box 22, Folder 4)
- Bank Deposits, 2000-2002 (Box 22, Folder 5)
- Forms and Contracts, 1999 (Box 22, Folder 6)
- Accounts Receivable, 2000-2002 (Box 22, Folder 7)
- Accounts Payable, 2000-2002 (Box 22, Folder 8)
- Mortgage Bank, 2000-2002 (Box 22, Folder 9)
- Balance Sheets and Income Statements, 2000-2002 (Box 22, Folder 10)
- Paid Invoice Journals, 2000-2002 (Box 22, Folder 11)
- House Detail, 2000-2002 (Box 22, Folder 12)
- Envelopes, 2000-2002 (Box 22, Folder 13)
- Pledge Manuals, Alphabetic listing, History, 2000-2002 (Box 22, Folder 14)
- Checkbooks, 1970s (Box 22, Folder 15)
- Initiation banquet programs, 1930, 1936 (Box 22, Folder 16)
- Miscellaneous photos in small box in Box 22, 2000-2002 (Box 22)
- Composites, miscellaneous photos, 1968-2008 (Box 23)
- CD's: Cornell Songs - CD-974 (Box 24, Folder 1)
- Episode of the television show Strange Days with Bob Saget, "How to Pledge and Be Hazed by an Ivy League Fraternity" - DVD-721 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  This epsiode features Bob Saget's visit to Ithaca and time spent with the fraternity.
- Additions and Alterations to 205 Thurston Ave., 1982 (Box 24, Folder 2)
- Fraternity Information, Social Events, Centennial Celebration, 2000-2007 (Box 24, Folder 3)
- The Snake, 1928-2007 (Box 24, Folder 4)
- Bills, Taxes, Contracts, Bursar Billings, 2004-2005 (Box 24, Folder 5)
- Invoices, 2004-2005 (Box 24, Folder 6)
- Accounts Payable/Receivable, 2004-2005 (Box 24, Folder 7)
- Correspondence, 2000-2006 (Box 24, Folder 8)
- Original fireplace bellows, ca. 1927 (Box 25)
- A Brief History of the Seal and Serpent Society, 19-- (Box 26, Folder 1)
- Activities Center Reference Manual, 1983-1985 (Box 26, Folder 2)
- Alumni Directory, 1991 (Box 26, Folder 3)
- Balance Sheets and President's Material, 1989-1990 (Box 26, Folder 4)
- Balance Sheets, 2004-2005 (Box 26, Folder 5)
- Board of Directors, 1957-1998 (Box 26, Folder 6)
- Bylaws, 1958 (Box 26, Folder 7)
- Campus Organization Directory, 1983-1984 (Box 26, Folder 8)
- Chapter Assessment, 1984 (Box 26, Folder 9)
- Cornell Daily Sun Clippings, 1985 (Box 26, Folder 10)
- Cornell Housing Referral Service, 1989-1990 (Box 26, Folder 11)
- Correspondence A-G, 1957-1961 (Box 26, Folder 12)
- Correspondence H-Z, 1958-1960 (Box 26, Folder 13)
- Correspondence from Alumni, 1996-2001 (Box 26, Folder 14)
- Correspondence to Alumni, 1959-1996 (Box 26, Folder 15)
- Deposit Slips, 2004-2005 (Box 26, Folder 16)
- Draft of The Snake, 1991 (Box 26, Folder 17)
- Epsilon Sigs, 1984 (Box 26, Folder 18)
- Founder's Fund, 1987-1989 (Box 26, Folder 19)
- Goals for Officers, 1989-1991 (Box 26, Folder 20)
- Goals, Plans, Visioning, 2000-2001 (Box 26, Folder 21)
- Hell Week, 1998 (Box 26, Folder 22)
- Homecoming, 1984-1991 (Box 26, Folder 23)
- House Accounts - Audit, 1960 (Box 26, Folder 24)
- Housing Contracts, 2004-2005 (Box 26, Folder 25)
- Interfraternity Council, 1958-1986 (Box 26, Folder 26)
- Interfraternity Council Information Packet, 1971-1972 (Box 26, Folder 27)
- Letter Format for Pledge Parents, 1960 (Box 26, Folder 28)
- Meeting Minutes, 1960 (Box 26, Folder 29)
- Miscellaneous Papers, 1980-2002 (Box 26, Folder 30)
  Includes a September 16, 1996 Time magazine
- Officers Person Papers, 1983-1986 (Box 26, Folder 31)
- Organizational Plans, 1958 (Box 26, Folder 32)
- Photographs, 1953-1999 (Box 26, Folder 33)
  Includes photos of 1953-1955 members
- Pledge Manual, 1988 (Box 26, Folder 34)
- President Donald Emery Papers, 1987 (Box 26, Folder 35)
- Records of Living Alumni, 1984 (Box 26, Folder 36)
- Recruitment Material, 1959-1989 (Box 26, Folder 37)
- Refurnishing Information, 1982 (Box 26, Folder 38)
- Renovation Plans (Box 26, Folder 39)
- Renovation Plans, 1981-1983 (Box 26, Folder 40)
- Social Events Material, 1938-1992 (Box 26, Folder 41)
- Stewart Howe Alumni Service, 1984-1985 (Box 26, Folder 42)
- Student Management Corporation, 1989-1990 (Box 26, Folder 43)
- Taxes, 2004-2005 (Box 26, Folder 44)
- The Snake, 1914-1980 (Box 26, Folder 45)
- The Snake, 1981-1996 (Box 26, Folder 46)
- Treasurer's Reports, 1957-1965 (Box 26, Folder 47)
- Construction plans for Lodge, Gibb & Waltz, Architects, Ithaca, New York, 6 pictures, October 27, 1926 and n.d. (Mapcase-folder 1-2)
- Specifications for mason and carpenter work; electrical wiring work; plumbing and gas fitting; Gibb & Waltz, 3 items, October 27, 1926 (Mapcase-folder 1-2)
- Plans for planting arrangement, Joseph P. Porter, landscape architect, Ithaca, New York, plan no. 80-A, 11 copies, March 1928 (Mapcase-folder 1-2)
- Temporary prints not to be used for construction; Gibb & Waltz, architects; 8 blueprints attached, rev. December 23, 1926 (Mapcase-folder 1-2)